inkthemes.com 2019-12-25

# Privacy Policy | InkThemes

This Privacy Policy was last modified and published on May 24, 2018, and will take effect on May 25, 2018.

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
  * We will protect and process personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
    * ####  **Data Processing outside the EEA**

If you are resident in the European Union, please note that as we are located in India (Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh), when you provide us with your Personal Information we will process it in countries outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”), such as India, which may not provide the same level of data protection as in your jurisdiction. This is necessary in order to perform our services. Regardless of where your Personal Information is located, we will adopt measures to protect your Personal Information as set out below.

      *  **How We Protect Your Information** We care about the integrity and security of your Personal Information and implement appropriate technical and organizational security measures to safeguard your Personal Information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or guarantee that your information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. Your privacy settings may also be affected by changes to the functionality of our distributors, such as social networks. We are not responsible for the functionality or security measures of any third party.

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you access to your account. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information, and for controlling access to your email communications from us, at all times.

      *  **Compromise of Personal Information** In the event that Personal Information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, we will promptly notify those persons whose Personal Information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law.
    * ####  **Your Choices About Your Information**

 **EEA Residents**

If you are located in the EEA, or if otherwise required by applicable law, you also have the following rights in relation to your information:

      *  **Inspection and access** : you can request from us a summary and a copy of any Personal Information we hold about you;
      *  **Correction/addition/removal** : where you believe your information is inaccurate or incomplete, you are entitled to request us to correct, amend or delete it;
      *  **Portability** : you may request that we send you any Personal Information that you have provided to us or ask that we send this information to a third party;
      *  **Objection** : you may object to us using your Personal Information where we use it based on our legitimate interests to do so;
      *  **Restriction** : you may request that we restrict the processing of your information where you believe it is inaccurate, our processing is unlawful, you believe we no longer need the information or if you have objected to our use of it; and
      *  **Automated Decision Making** : where we undertake automated decision making (including profiling), which significantly affects you, you are entitled to object to such decision-making.

####  **  
** **All Users**

      *  **Decline to Submit Information**  – You may, of course, decline to submit Personal Information through the Service, in which case we may not be able to provide certain services to you.
      *  **Update Account Information** – You may update or correct your account information and email preferences at any time by logging in to your account settings page. You can also exercise any of your rights by contacting us directly at enquiry@formget.com
      *  **Unsubscribe from emails** – To unsubscribe from a particular newsletter, click the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of that email newsletter. When we send newsletters to subscribers we may allow advertisers or partners to include messages in those newsletters, or we may send dedicated newsletters and marketing messages on behalf of those advertisers or partners. We may disclose your opt-out choices to third parties so that they can honor your preferences in accordance with applicable laws.
      *  **Blocking cookies** – Certain browsers may be configured to notify you when you receive cookies or allow you to restrict or disable certain cookies. If you choose to disable cookies, however, that could affect certain features of the Service that use cookies to enhance their functionality.
      *  **Disabling local shared objects (e.g., Flash cookies)** – We may use other kinds of local storage that function similarly but are stored in different parts of your computer from ordinary browser cookies, including Flash cookies placed on your device or web browser via the Adobe Flash plug-in. Your browser may allow you to disable its HTML5 local storage or delete information contained in its HTML5 local storage.
      * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
      * We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

####  **Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

We may update its Privacy Policy from time to time, and so you should review this Policy periodically. When we change the policy in a material way, we will update the ‘last modified’ date at the top of this Privacy Policy. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

####  **Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this website, please contact us at enquiry@inkthemes.com
